vark.com 2010-01-07

# Aardvark

Aardvark values the privacy of its users. This Privacy Notice outlines the details of Aardvark's commitment to user privacy. Feel free to email [privacy@themechanicalzoo.com](mailto:privacy@themechanicalzoo.com) with any questions about Aardvark policies regarding personal information and privacy.

###### Information Collection & Use

##### Registration

In order to use Aardvark, you must first complete the registration process. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the Aardvark services in which you have expressed interest.

The Mechanical Zoo is the sole owner of the information collected on Vark.com and any related Aardvark products and robots. The Mechanical Zoo collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site and related products.

##### Invite a Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. The Mechanical Zoo stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [privacy@themechanicalzoo.com](mailto:privacy@themechanicalzoo.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

###### Communications from Aardvark

##### Service-related Announcements and Notifications

We will send you strictly service-related announcements.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

##### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

##### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and explicit interactions with the service to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile, in order to improve the content of the service for you.

We do not share your profile with other third parties.

###### Information Sharing and Disclosure

##### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners. This information does not identify individual users.

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

##### Personally identifiable information

We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties

##### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

###### Log Files

As is true of most Web services, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We use third-party tracking services called Reinvigorate and Google Analytics that track visitors to our site.

###### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site.

###### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by The Mechanical Zoo. Please be aware that we, The Mechanical Zoo, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

###### User Forums

If you use the user forum on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

###### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support@vark.com](mailto:support@vark.com) or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.

###### Business Transitions

In the event The Mechanical Zoo goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

###### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

###### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy,   
please contact us at:  
The Mechanical Zoo  
138 10th Street  
San Francisco, CA 94103
